Guide to the Administrative Papers of the President George Bugliarello RG.006
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series I: Subject Files
  - Subseries A: Alphabetical Files
    - Fialkov, Herman – Poly Ventures, 1982 March-1990 March (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Filner, Joseph H., 1992 May (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Poly-University Financial Statement – Independent Auditors Report, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Fink, Honorable Stanley, 1981 February-1983 June (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Finkelstein, Edward S., 1977 March-1979 January (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Finland – Trip, 1991 May-1992 September (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Fischer, George Prof., 1973 November-1988 December (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Fisher, Robert J., 1983 July-1988 February (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Flack, James, 1986 October-1989 September (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Florida, 1990 July-1993 January (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Foecke, Harold A., 1987 October-December (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Food Science, 1973 September-1975 November (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Foucault, Pierre-Max - CONFIDENTIAL, 1987 October (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Foxen, Richard W., 1976 April-1988 February (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Frank, Danny, 1974 July-1989 June (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Frankel, Arnold, 1986 August-1990 January (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Freedman, Debra, 1982 June-1990 April (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - French, Frank, 1991 October (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Frieman, Dr. Edward, 1984 May-1987 October (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Friend, William, 1983 October-1989 March (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Friend, William, 1989 April-1992 May (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Fusaroli, Dr. Paolo - Trieste University, 1982 November-1991 March (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Fusfeld, Dr. Hubert I., 1985 January-1987 May (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Future of Bioengineering Chemical Proofs, 1994 March-April (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Fyodorov Fyodorovich, Professor Boris, 1990 January-October (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Faa – Feinsot – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1966-1990 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Feldberg – Feynman – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1984-1989 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Fialkov- Flack – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1976-1990 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Flagle – Friedland – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1975-1990 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Frackman-Fyodor – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1973-1990 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Galloway, Dr. Ethan C., 1989 August-1991 July (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Gambardella, Alfonso, 1984 December-1986 March (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Gavin, Joseph G. Jr., 1976 December-1985 April (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Gayl, Franz J.F., 1978 January-April (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Ghetti, Augusto, 1984 December-1990 July (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Giardina, Emilio, 1986 September-October (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Giardina, Emilio, 1985 October-1989 August (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Giba, John J., 1987 April-1992 March (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Giba, John J., 1991 May-1993 July (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Gibbons, John Howard, 1993 January (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Giglio, Joseph M. Jr., 1991 August (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Giordano, Anthony, 1969 May-1983 October (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Giordano, Anthony, 1985 August-1991 June (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Giovannini, Giovani, 1989 January-November (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Gold, Albert, 1979 July-1981 August (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Golden, Hon. Howard, 1979 May-1992 September (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Golden, William T., 1974 October-1982 April (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Golden, William T., 1983 August-1992 April (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Goldsmith, Clifford H., 1984 June-1990 January (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Goldstein, Michael B., 1978 August-1982 October (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Gomory, Ralph, 1986 September-1990 February (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Good, Mary and Bill Jewel, 1989 October (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Goodman, Alan, 1985 November-1988 August (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Goodman, Harold L., 1986 July (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Goodman, Louis J., 1977 May-1986 December (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Goodman, Louis J., 1987 October-1991 September (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Goonatilake, Susantha, 1992 March (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Goulard, Robert, 1974 November-December (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Gourman Report Ratings, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Governor's Policy Steering Committee, 1990 July (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - W.R. Grace & Company, 1966 December-1983 May (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Grad, Arthur, 1971 July-1973 January (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Grau, Herman, 1975 October-1989 July (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Graubard, Stephen R., 1984 December-1988 July (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Grayson, Dr. Lawrence, 1975 July-1990 January (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Great Projects Film Company, 1988 May-1989 May (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Greco, Bill, 1981 March-1989 September (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Greece, Athens – NATO, 1981 July-1983 August (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Greece, Athens – NATO, 1983 September-1987 October (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Green, Mark M., 1979 October-1990 March (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Green, Roger L., 1987 April-1989 June (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Green, Bill, 1987 June-1989 November (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Griswold, Albert, 1989 May (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Gruber, Professor Helmut, 1986 September-1987 January (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - GTE Corporation – November 1984-December 1988, 1984 November-1988 December (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Guggino, Emanuel, 1973 October-1978 May (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Guggino, Emanuel, 1978 October-1982 November (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Guggino, Emanuel, 1983 January-1988 April, Undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Gummel, Dr. Hermann K., 1985 June-August (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Gaffney – Georgiou – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1979-1990 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Gergen – Gluck – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1968-1990 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Goldsmith – Gymnasium – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1975-1990 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Gomory – Goz – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1974-1989 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Government – Gomez – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1977-1990 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Grab-GPA – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1970-1990 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Haller, Jordan, 1989 July-1990 August (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Halpern, Dr. George, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Helsinki Trip, 1991 April-1992 February (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Hill, Christopher, 1987 January (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Hill, Lester Owen, 1987 July (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Hochstadt, Harry, 1972 May-1990 April (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Hoffman, Roald, 1991 January-February (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Horn, Dr. Harry M., 1986 December-1987 January (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Horwitch, Mel, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Howard, Rio, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Hrones, John A., 1970 December-1971 June (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Hughes, Harold, 1969 May-1976 June (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Hung, Tin Kan, 1974 July-1977 December (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Hung, Tin Kan, 1979 May-1987 September (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - University of Illinois – Energy Conference, 1995 August-1996 June (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Immergut, Dr. Edmund H., 1975 September-1990 June (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Inauguration (letter from Ephraim Katzir, president of Israel), 1974 January-1975 February (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Inauguration, 1975 March-1976 August (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - International Conference on Unity of the Sciences, 1976 November (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - IAFE (International Association of Financial Engineers), 1995 October-June (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - IAFE, 1995 July-1996 October (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - IAFE, 1996 November-1997 January, Undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Innovare, S.R.L., 1991 April-1995 September, Undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Polytechnic - Institutional Advancement Committee, 1995 May (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Iran, 1976 April-June (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Iran, 1976 June-1978 June (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Iraq, 1991 March (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Italy Trip – Notes & Slides, 1991 January (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Italian Visitors to Polytechnic, 1987 September (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Italy- Professor Paul R. DeCicco, 1968 February-1974 April (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Italy – Miscellaneous, 1974 January-1992 October (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Italian Publications, 1972-1992 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Italian Management Visit, 1990 August-December (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Jankovic, Milos, Undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Japan & Taiwan, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Japanese Mission to the U.S., 1990 April (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Japan, 1990 March-1991 September (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Japan, 1990 October-1991 March (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Jonsson, Erik J.D., 1978 April-1986 September (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Jonsson, Erik J.D., 1986 November-1993 March (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Kaiser, Arthur, 1987 February (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Kane, Jasper H., 1992 October (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Kaspar, Dr. Jan, 1989 May-July (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Katzen, Dr. Raphael - RESTRICT, 1988 January-1990 August (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Kaufman, Michael, 1992 April-June (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Klein, Hon. Genevieve S., 1982 February-1987 Janaury (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Kleiner, Eugene – Trustee, 1993 June (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Kobayashi, Dr. Koji, 1974 September-1988 August (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Koch, Mayor Edward, 1975 August-1988 August (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Kroll, Jules – Kroll Associates, 1993 March-1995 March (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - LaCorte, John, 1988 March-1989 April (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Lalkaka, Rustam, 1987 April-1989 November (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Landau, Ralph, 1980 April-1988 November (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Lang, Eugene M., 1987 September (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Larocca, James L., May 1979-1985 June (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Larson, Elwin S., 1986 July-1990 April (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Laubach, Gerald D., 1980 October–1985 December (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - League of Women Voters, 1980 January, 1987 December (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Learning Center, 1988 May-1990 June (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Lederberg, Dr. Joshua, 1980 December-1989 November (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Leistner, William E., 1970 February-1983 August (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Lenefsky, David, 1976 July-1989 February (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Leonard, Martha, 1983 August-1990 June (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Leonard, Martha, 1985 June-1990 June (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Leung, K.M., 1990 May-1992 August (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Levi, Enzo, 1975 November-1976 June (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Levin, Honorable Wilbur A., 1989 December-1990 July (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Levine, Rosalie, 1986 January-February (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Levy, Stephen L., 1980 November-1989 October (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Levy, Stephen L., 1980 December-1982 February (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Library – Polytechnic University, 1987 September-1990 June (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Likourezos, George E., 1991 June-December (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Linden, Henry R., 1983 May-1989 June (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Litton Industries, 1978 October-1990 February (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Lizardos, Evans J., 1986 March-1990 April (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Logan, Dr. John A., 1978 December-1979 March (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Logica, Undated (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Lombardino, Joseph, 1988 September (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Long Island, 1976 June-1990 June (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Loral Fairchild Systems, Inc., 1988 August-1989 October (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Lord Corporation, 1980 February-1990 March (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Lotti, Carlo, 1975 May-1988 December (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Henry Luce Foundation, Inc., 1976 May-1989 October (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Luntey, Eugene – Brooklyn Union Gas Company, 1975 July-1988 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Luow, J.M., 1980 August-1987 March (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Lab-Lan – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1976-1990 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - LaSala-Lew – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1981-1990 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Lic-Lom – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1978-1990 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Long-Ly – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1977-1990 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Machanik, Jack, 1986 April-1989 March (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Machol, Dr. Robert, 1986 May-1988 February (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - MacGrath, Francis F., 1990 May-July (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Mack, Lynn, 1981 September-1985 March (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - MacVicar, Margaret, 1986 March-1988 February (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Maglich, Dr. Bogdan, 1982 January-1984 December (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Malik, Mazhar Ali Khan, 1991 January-1992 September (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Mancuso, Michael A. Jr., 1975 December-1977 June (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Mandel, Kenneth, 1985 January-1986 May (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Mandery, Matthew M., 1985 May-1988 November (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Mannielo, John, 1971 May-1992 August (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Manzo, Edward D., 1982 February-1985 May (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Marcisz, Thomas J., 1974 June-1978 June (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Marcus, Dr. Rudolph, 1993 January-February (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Marcuvitz, Nathan, 1984 November-1989 April (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Margolin, Harold, 1976 March-1990 February (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Marino, Peter A., 1988 July-1993 May (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Mark, Hans Michael (Secretary of the Air Force and former Deputy Administrator of NASA), 1975 May-1983 December (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Mark, Hans Michael, 1983 June-1992 April (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Mark, Dr. Herman F., 1961 June-1975 December (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Mark, Dr. Herman F., 1976 January-1985 November (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Mark, Dr. Herman F., 1986 March-1989 September (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Mark, Dr. Herman F., 1990 April-1992 October, Undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Marsh, Josh O., Jr., 1980 January-1986 July (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Marsh, Mary H., 1988 February-March (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Marshak, Robert E., 1989 November-1990 April (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Marshall, Charles, 1988 September-1989 April (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Martino, Gregory – RESTRICT, 1993 March (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Martino, Peter V., 1986 May, 1987 November (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1984 October-1989 November (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Massey, Walter E., 1989 May-1992 March (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Massey, Walter E., 1992 April, Undated (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Mastronardi Center, 1974 October-1979 February (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Maxwell, Howard B., 1987 December-1990 August (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Maxwell, Robert, 1987 February-1991 September (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - May, William F., 1968 September-1987 August (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Mayo, Dr. John S., 1987 June-1993 February (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Mazaika, Michael A., 1985 October-1987 October (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - McFall, Russell W., 1965 May-August (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - McFate, Patricia, 1985 April-1988 August (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - McKeen, John E., 1975 January-1977 June (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - McKenzie, Peter, 1993 June (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - McLean, Noel B., 1965 February-1972 April (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - McLeod, Stuart R., 1974 November-1975 July (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - McQuade, Charles, 1992 May (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - McShane, William, 1986 January-1990 March (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Meak, Raimondo, 1988 March-July (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Mega-Cities, 1988 August - 1990 May (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Menashe, Louis, 1984 August-1990 April (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Mendik, Bernard H., 1983 September-1985 April (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Mendik, Bernard H., 1983 September-1985 April (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Menes, Meir, 1974 November-1978 May (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Merck Company, 1987 March-1988 July (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Merlino, Silvana - RESTRICT, 1991 February (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Messina, Carlo, 1991 July-October (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Metro-International, 1986 January-1989 October (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Metropolitan Transit Authority, 1979 February-1989 November (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Metzer, Sidney, 1976 September-1992 November (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Meyerson, Martin - University of Pennsylvania President, 1969 May-1976 December (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Cassa del Mezzogiorno, 1967 April-1978 February (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Cassa del Mezzogiorno, 1978 March-November (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Michel, Jean, 1988 December-1989 January (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Michelson, G.G., 1993 February (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Middendorf, Henry Q., 1985 January-1989 May (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Midwood High School, 1987 April-June (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Miller, Irving F., 1983 March-1986 March (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Miranda, Robert N., 1975 August-1985 April (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Mishkin, Eli A., 1974 October-1979 December (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Mishkin, Eli A., 1980 March-1985 September (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Mishkin, Eli A., 1979 November-1982 November (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Mitcham, Carl, 1977 May-1990 January (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Mitchell, David L., 1974 November-1983 August (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Mog, David M., 1985 July-1990 January (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Monte, Nick, 1981 July-1989 July (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Montgomery, Velmanette, 1985 November-December (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Morancie, Michelle D. - RESTRICT, 1981 June (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Morawetz, Herbert, 1975 September-1987 May (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Moretti, Gino, 1975 June-1989 March (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Morgan, James I., 1988 October-1989 May (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Morgan Stanley, 1986 May-1989 July (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Morison, Dr. Elting, 1975 September-1989 November (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Moscow, 1990 February-1991 July (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Mott, Colonel Frank E., 1975 April-June (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Motzkin, Shirley, 1974 December-1991 September (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick, 1976 June-1989 November (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Herman Muchlstein Foundation, 1982 June-February (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Mukherjee, Dr. Kali, 1980 May-1986 February (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Munro, J. Richard, 1983 March-1986 August (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Murdock, Wilbur, 1989 July (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Murphy, Arthur T., 1988 September-1989 March (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Murray, William R., 1987 May-1990 April (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Musco, Professor Alessandra, 1989 February-1990 January (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Musto, Professor Ing. Francesco, 1984 December-1989 July (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Myers, Robert J., 1989 February-October (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Myerson, Allan, 1987 July-1989 August (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Ma-Manuv– Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1976-1990 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Manz-Maz – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1982-1990 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Mc – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1969-1990 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Me-Mez – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1975-1990 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Mir-Mur – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1966-1990 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Mi-Min – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1974-1990 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Murp-My – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1973-1990 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Nalecz, Dr. Maciej Z., 1979 August-1992 June (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Napolitano, 1989 June-1991 August (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Nardo, Sebastian Vincent, 1988 May-December (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Nasmith, Augustus Dr., 1984 February-1988 November (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - National Academy of Engineers – Program Report, 1984-1990 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - National Academy of Engineers, 1989 August-December (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1974 October, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - National Research Council, 1981 May-1990 April (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - National Research Council, 1991 March-April (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - National Research Council, 1991 July-1992 July (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - National Research Council, 1992 June-October (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - National Research Council, 1991 March-April (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - National Research Council – Board Meeting Materials, 1992 March-June (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - National Satellite Services, 1983 August-1988 November (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Nelson, Theodore W., 1977 June-1978 September (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Nerken, Albert – Nerken Center, 1989 November-1990 May (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Nespoli, Paolo A., 1985 July-1988 November (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Newell, James F., 1991 August-September (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Newman, Joseph H., 1979 December-1987 September (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - New Orleans – National Trustee Workshop, 1983 August-October (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - SUNY New Paltz, 1984 April-June (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Newsday, 1978 October-1985 Febraury (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Newsweek – Letter to the Editor, 1994 August (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - New York Academy of Science, 1987 July-October (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - New York City Partnership – New York: How to Get To The 21st Century, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - New York City Technical Assistance Center, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers, 1990 March (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - New York State Commission on Science & Technology, 1987 March (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - New York State Science & Technology Foundation, 1987 March-October (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - New York State Society of Professional Engineers, 1987 February-April (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - New York Telephone, 1987 June-December (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - New York University, 1983 June-1989 October (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Nichols, Alan, 1978 February-1989 October (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Nielsen, John, 1976 March-1989 August (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Nishijima, Yasunori, 1986 December-1990 April (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - N-Nat – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1978-1990 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Nau-New – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1982-1990 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - New York – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1974-1990 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Nic-Nix – Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1978-1989 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Oakland University – Speech, November 13, 1984, 1984 July-1985 January (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Oakland University – Speech, November 13, 1984 – Notes, Undated (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Organisation De Cooperation et de Developpement Economiques (OECD), Undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - O.E.C.D. – Portugal, 1970 January-1983 January (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - O.E.C.D. – Portugal, 1983 February-1984 May (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - O.E.C.D. – Portugal, 1984 June-1990 September (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - O.E.C.D. – Portugal, 1991 June-1992 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - O.E.C.D. – Portugal, 1990 October-1991 March (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - O.E.C.D. – Portugal – Publications, Undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - O.E.C.D - Portugal - Oversize, 1990 October 3 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Othmer, Donald, 1993 October, 1994 September (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Ottawa Symposium, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Ottawa Symposium, 1976 March-1991 January, Undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Paley, Henry, 1973 October-1975 November (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Palm Springs, California – Higher Education Executive Conference, 1990 February-March (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Papadakis, Constantine N., 1993 April (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Polytechnic University– Executive Committee Notes, Undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Polytechnic University – Protocol, 1985 September-1988 June (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Polytechnic University - Question & Answer Brochure, 1988 September-October (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Polytechnic University – Telephone Directory, 1992, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Pond, Jules, 1952, 1974 October-1981 March (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Proskaver, Dr. Eric, 1988 September (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Pusey, Nathan Marsh, 1974 December-1975 December (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Radley, Melanie L., 1985 June-December (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Reiss Romoli, 1989 June-1990 December (Box 12, Folder 18)